(Space Rice Cake)
(To find the leader of Space Rice Cake,)
(the head chef cook-off was held.)
Why are you messing with my mind?
(Through the fierce competition,)
(the winner was decided.)
Neapolitan Tteokfia.
(The head chef is Lee Young Ji.)
(And they...)
(The crossroads of space and Earth)
(They head to Goheung.)
(Honesty!)
(Humility!)
(One, two, three)
(Ahk!)
(Wait, it's not cut.)
(A bad omen from the start. What lies ahead for Space Rice Cake?)
- Can we go inside and take a look?
- Yes. It's the only restaurant...
- Gosh. What do we do?
- You can go in through that door.
This place has the old-school restaurant vibe.
- Seriously...
- It really does.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Why?
- It's so pretty.
- It's really nice.
Tteokbokki with an ocean view!
- The kitchen is large.
- It's so nice.
(Let us show you around the first Earth location of Space Rice Cake.)
- My, this place is so nice.
- Look at this.
This is insanely beautiful.
(The main kitchen where tasty dishes will be created)
- It's nice.
- Mimi, it's so nice.
It's awesome.
- It's really beautiful.
- There's a stove here.
Let's say "tteokbokki with an ocean view." Ready, go.
- Tteokbokki with an ocean view!
(The refreshing ocean view from the stove)
Am I bossy? Mimi.
(Even though they bicker from time to time...)
(The deeply bonded chefs will showcase their skills here.)
- It's amazing.
- Indeed.
- This is where we make desserts.
- Right.
This is where we make desserts.
(Next to the main kitchen...)
(Sub-kitchen)
(Sweet desserts will be made here.)
Look at these plates. Mimi likes dishware.
- They're cute.
- We have plates here.
They have Torong on them.
- It says, "Hey, Torong."
- This is where...
Eun Ji and Yu Jin will work busily.
This is a bit too low for me.
- Hold on.
- On top of that, more importantly,
the floor is sloped here.
- It's high enough for me.
- It's easy to move around here.
It's perfect for me.
- It's because Yu Jin is tall.
- Is it too low for her?
- Did you see this machine here?
- This is driving me crazy.
A machine? Oh, I guess we're making our own rice cake.
- Exactly. Look at this.
- We're making our own rice cake.
I guess we're making our own rice cake.
- I suppose we are. I'm worried.
- What is this?
Look at this, Young Ji.
Hold on a second. Head Chef.
- I'm so shocked right now.
- I see.
Nobody told us we'd have to make rice cake.
Think about it. If we make our own rice cake here,
we are going to... I'm not joking.
We are going to...
- get wiped out.
- We'll have to...
We'll have to wake up at 2am.
Actually, we weren't planning on bringing the machine.
We did it because Young Ji said she wanted to make rice cake.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, Chef Lee.
- I mean...
- Chef Lee.
- You said you wanted to use...
freshly made rice cake for your tteokbokki.
- That's why we brought the machine.
- Chef Lee.
(By any chance, do we have a machine for garaetteok?)
(As Chef Lee made an unexpected request...)
(I used freshly made rice cake during the cook-off,)
(and I realised it yields the best results.)
(- Freshly made ones are the best.
- We'll do our best to pull it off.)
(The staff did their best to make it happen.)
- What should we do?
- How could you make that call...
- all by yourself, Chef Lee?
- How could you do that, Chef Lee?
I didn't know we would have a rice cake machine...
- in Goheung.
- You should have...
asked us first.
- "We'll make our own rice cake."
- Exactly.
- I didn't know they'd bring this.
- But you see,
- she said it in passing.
- That's right.
It was just like saying, "We can make 100,000 dollars..."
"and buy a fancy car with that money."
I never knew they'd actually bring a rice cake machine.
- Let's just take a look at it.
- Also...
- Mind what you say from now on.
- Yes? Go ahead.
Also, we set something up here to help you...
measure the size of the rice cakes.
Is this 175cm long?
- Would you like to pull it out?
- Oh, here it is.
- She said we should do it together.
- This is the regular size.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
(Peekaboo)
- Gosh. Hold on a second.
- You wanted rice cakes...
that were as tall as you.
- So we set this up.
- Hold on.
- Hang on.
- You invested too much money...
- in this business, don't you think?
- It's cute.
- When you pull this out...
- That's it.
- That's how far it can slide out.
- Hang on.
- Hold on. Give me a second.
(They will make good use of it.)
Young Ji, you have nice legs.
- It's an AI-generated image, Mimi.
- Shall we move on?
- Yes, let's take a look over there.
- Let's go.
So this is where we serve food...
Is this a private room?
- Is there a private room too?
- Yes.
- Like a fine dining restaurant.
- What?
- This is a fine dining restaurant.
- Guys, look.
(Down the hall from the kitchen...)
(Main hall)
(4 tables are lined up side by side.)
We can play Guess Who Quiz here. Look at Neapolitan Matfia.
Hello.
- You startled me.
- Did you think he was here?
Young Ji, shouldn't it be your photo instead of his?
(Senior Torong and Manager Kwon?)
(Charming and cosy decorative items fill the room.)
(We wish you great success.)
(Let's aim for opening a 2nd location!)
You're so pretty, just like an idol singer.
- Me? I'm an idol singer.
- Right?
(People share kind words with each other here.)
(It's a place enjoyed by people of all ages and genders.)
(What wonderful memories will be created here?)
May I ask how full you are right now?
Don't worry. We ate a lot.
Guys, we have outdoor tables as well.
(The romantic spot, exclusively at Space Rice Cake)
This place is so beautiful.
This is amazing.
It has a really good vibe.
I really love this vibe.
(Come visit us!)
- The weather is beautiful today.
- It's awesome.
It's so nice here.
Guys, let's make a lot of money and buy this place.
- Exactly. The location is perfect.
- It's really nice.
Many of your senior entertainers sent flowers.
- Who?
- Mr. Lee Kwang Soo!
- Yes.
- Mr. Lee Seo Jin!
- That's amazing.
- What?
- That one is from Torong.
- Which one?
It says, "rice cake..."
- It's from Ms. Youn Yuh Jung.
- Oh, my.
Those are from the cast of "Kang's Kitchen."
Most of them are the cast of old restaurant shows...
- produced by egg is coming.
- That's right.
- They're not imposters, right?
- I think you borrowed their names.
- Exactly. You borrowed their names.
- Are they imposters?
I'm sure Ms. Youn Yuh Jung has no idea...
(Let's move on to the next part of our ceremony.)
- We prepared a small ceremony...
- A traditional ritual?
- to wish for good luck.
- Look at the pig.
How about each of you makes a wish before we open the restaurant?
- She's bowing right away.
- Young Ji, wait. Come back here.
- Young Ji, come back here.
- You should say your wish out loud.
Young Ji, it's not like we have 600 cameras around us.
(Start over again.)
- Mimi, you go first.
- You can call this a main event.
I wish for the good health of everyone here.
I hope nobody gets hurt or slips and falls.
- And I hope we never fight.
- "I hope we never fight."
I hope we fight and go viral with ten million views.
She must be Buddhist.
- Is this how Buddhists bow?
- Yes.
(Next up is Yu Jin.)
- Make a wish with all your heart.
- With sincerity.
- Make sure of it.
- I hope I don't get hurt...
using a knife in the kitchen.
- I hope the girls never fight.
- We all wish for the same thing.
I also hope my cuteness shines through.
Can't you make a wish for the whole team too?
- She wants her cuteness to shine.
- What does she mean by that?
Next up is Eun Ji, who recently wrapped up her radio show.
She must feel liberated.
- Finally...
- She claims to be human arginine.
Human arginine.
We're opening up a restaurant.
I'm so afraid.
- I'm so afraid too.
- Please help us.
(Please grant us courage.)
- Honestly, - This is a traditional ritual.
this restaurant is so nice that I want to invite my friends.
- I agree.
- It'd be nice if you do.
- Invite some of your friends.
- Who would come all the way here?
(It's a 10-hour round trip from Seoul.)
All the members of "Earth Arcade..."
If we're going to fight, let's make sure it's caught on camera.
If anyone's pants fall down, it has to be on camera.
Even if we face conflicts, competition, or hardships,
I hope we can get through them.
Head chefs rarely wear sagging pants.
- She's a next-generation chef.
- A next-generation chef.
Why are you eating the apple?
- That will bring bad luck.
Young Ji, discuss your every move before you actually make them.
- I suddenly feel anxious.
- About what?
- I'm anxious now.
- What...
What are we going to do after this ceremony?
What is the main ingredient...
- of Young Ji's dish?
- Yes?
- Rice cake.
- Correct.
- You need to learn how to make it.
- Okay.
- Let's gather here after a break.
- I'm already dressed comfortably.
(They're taking a short break.)
(However...)
Hello.
We opened up a restaurant.
We serve tteokbokki.
- We're quite young.
- You serve tteokbokki?
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- She's our head chef.
- Please come for tteokbokki.
- I'm the head of the village.
- Oh, I see.
- The head of the village!
- Spread the word, please.
- Let's salute him.
- Honesty! Humility! Ahk!
- Humility! Ahk!
(They pledge allegiance to him right away.)
- Thank you.
Is "Ahkun" one of the cast members?
- It's actually "ahk."
- Abu Dhabi...
- In Dubai, it means "big brother."
- It's Arabic. "Big brother."
- "Big brother."
I'll visit your restaurant with my wife.
- Please do.
- That'd be great, sir.
- We'll have many customers, sir.
- Oh, there's...
(It's time to make rice cake.)
- Watch your head.
- Watch your head, please.
- Hello. Welcome to Space Rice Cake.
- Hello.
- I'll walk you through the process.
- Okay.
- I'll demonstrate it step-by-step.
- Step by step
So we're going to...
(The types of rice cakes they will learn today)
You'll learn how to make garaetteok for Young Ji's dish...
- and jeolpyeon for Mimi's.
- Jeolpyeon.
- It's basically thin garaetteok.
- Right.
The machines we'll be using are the rice grinder behind you...
- Got it. Rice grinder.
- Yes, that one is used...
- to grind rice.
- Yes.
- And this one is a steamer.
- Steamer.
- We use it to steam rice cakes.
- We can make baekseolgi with it.
- This machine is called jebyeonggi.
- Steamer.
It's a rice cake shaper.
We can shape our rice cakes...
- however we want.
- Right.
(Step 1: Soaking the rice)
You have to prepare the rice in advance.
You can just put the rice in water the night before...
- and store it in the fridge.
- I see.
(Step 2: Grinding the rice)
I'll tell you how to use the rice grinder.
- Okay.
- The rice grinder.
The grinding process consists of two stages.
- Add salt first and then water.
- I see.
Add salt equivalent to 1.2 percent of the rice's total weight.
(Add salt equivalent to 1.2 percent of the rice's total weight.)
(Bring the rice that was soaked overnight...)
(and weigh it on the scale.)
Okay.
- You have to multiply the numbers.
- Yes.
Me? I'm not good at math.
- We can do it together.
- Right.
Do any of you guys have a college degree?
No.
- Eun Ji, didn't you go to college?
- I have a college degree.
Then you do the math.
- I should calculate it?
- Yes.
I gave up on math when I was in the sixth grade. What do I do?
- It took you so long to give up.
- Exactly. This is driving me nuts.
- Multiply 6.2...
- Yes.
- by 0.012...
We should add 74.4g of salt.
- We're doing great.
- Can you prep this for me?
(Add salt and mix everything well.)
- One, two, three.
Let's pour it.
I think you can just dump it.
(Grinding)
That's fascinating.
- My, that's pretty.
- It's so fascinating.
It looks like shaved ice.
(The rice flour falls just like snow.)
Mimi, she said...
- you should multiply it by 150.
- Got it.
(Calculate the amount of water, add it, and then grind it again.)
(Stir the mixture gently so it doesn't clump together.)
Young Ji looks like...
a Gen Z entrepreneur opening up a restaurant...
- in Sindang-dong.
- A Gen Zer.
- Here we go. One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
Nice.
(Grind the mixture again with the rice grinder.)
(The finely ground rice flour is ready.)
I didn't know that it was this hard to make rice cake.
I guess that's why it's tasty.
Exactly. There's a reason why mills start working at 4am.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
Yu Jin's eyes look soulless. Get that on camera.
(I never looked like that.)
(Step 3: Steaming baekseolgi)
You just have to pour the rice flour into the container,
leaving about 1cm of space at the top.
- It's a lot.
- It smells good.
- It holds such a large amount.
- Exactly.
The center part looks perfect, so leave it as it is.
Just flatten the edges evenly.
- Even - Evenly
(The word triggers her performer instinct.)
- May I dance, Head Chef?
- Sure.
- Even, even - Now or never. Let's dance.
- Even, even - Nice.
- Thank you.
You have to open this to drain the water...
- Yes.
- in case there's water in there.
My goodness.
I wonder what lies at the edge of the vast ocean
- Right. That's our Eun Ji.
- There must be
(Atlantis Princess appears in Goheung.)
- She's a natural-born performer.
- She never lets us down.
Look at her flexing her cooking show experience.
Perform "Rebel Heart," please.
- We are rebels in our heart - We are rebels in our heart
(They're almost invisible.)
(The original singer is singing her heart out.)
Isn't it hot?
- It's warm.
- It's like a humidifier.
(Young Ji tries the steam therapy as well.)
Please sing "I Am Lee Young Ji" for us.
- I am Lee Young Ji - It just made a noise, right?
I'll turn this off now.
You just have to cover the rice cake with a damp cloth.
(Cover the container with a cloth and steam it for 20 minutes.)
(Cover it facing away from you so the steam doesn't burn you!)
After you cover it, the cloth puffs up...
- You covered it well.
- Yes.
Impressive. Nice.
When it puffs up, set the timer for 20 minutes.
- Set the timer for 20 minutes.
- Bring the timer.
(After 20 minutes, poke it with a chopstick.)
Look at this. It looks so tasty.
(Baekseolgi is done.)
(Step 4: Running the rice cake dough through the machine)
(Here's the thing about the rice cake shaper.)
So this is how it goes in.
Okay.
(Garaetteok)
(Jeolpyeon)
(The extruding nozzles determine the shape of the rice cake.)
It should be rinsed with water as it comes out of the machine.
So you need a basin filled with water.
And place that large rectangular strainer next to it.
(Line the drying strainer with food-safe plastic wrap.)
The next step requires two people.
One person pulls the rice cake out while measuring the length.
The other person stacks the rice cake in the strainer.
- You two can do this together.
- Okay.
Step behind the machine.
- I'll pull and you stack, okay?
- Sure.
(The 1st attempt at using the rice cake shaper)
You didn't cut off the tip.
Oh, no. Young Ji.
(The rice cake is flopping around helplessly.)
- Young Ji.
- Give me a second, Eun Ji.
Young Ji.
(It's supposed to look pretty as it comes out.)
My goodness. Young Ji.
(String cheese?)
Young Ji, what do we do with this?
(Both Young Ji and the rice cake...)
(are worn out.)
I can't get the hang of it.
- How about I stack it?
- Okay. You do that.
I'm ready.
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
(Despite her cheerful spirit, she's all over the place from the start.)
- Young Ji. I couldn't do it.
- Eun Ji, put it in the water.
I couldn't put it in the water.
(Crying)
Eun Ji,
- we messed this up.
- We messed it up?
- We messed it up. Please stop.
- We really did.
Eun Ji, let's switch places again.
Let's switch again.
It's still not working. What do we do?
(4th attempt)
Keep the length even and take it slow.
(6th attempt)
Here we go.
(7th attempt)
Director Ye Seul, this is hard.
- You can do it.
- Why is it so sticky?
I think we used it too many times.
- It developed too much gluten.
- Yes.
(Tired)
Young Ji, I have a good feeling about this.
Why don't you adjust it in the water when it comes out?
- I should.
- You can adjust it in the water.
- Okay, let's try that.
- Yes.
This is our last try.
- Stretching it in the water.
- In the water.
In the water.
(The shaper is back on.)
It's working.
- Yes.
- It's working.
- While you shape it...
- This...
- This should be enough.
- That's good.
That's great.
Perfect. It really worked.
We got it.
I ran the rice cake through the machine without breaking it.
Doesn't it look amazing?
- How is it?
- Isn't it amazing?
- Nice.
- That was nice.
- You did such a great job.
- It looks beautiful.
(It's time to taste the freshly made rice cake.)
How is it?
(Exclaiming)
(Humming)
- It's delicious.
- It's so good.
(Completely absorbed in eating)
(Exclaiming)
- How is it?
- It's amazing.
(I made it, but it's really good.)
Are we running a tteokbokki place or a rice cake shop?
- A tteokbokki place.
- Or both.
(The question naturally comes up after 2 hours of making rice cakes.)
Just because...
I said I wanted to make rice cakes by hand,
you went and got the rice cake shaper,
the steamer, and the grinder.
Isn't this a little too much?
With all these machines,
spending eight hours straight making rice cakes...
and cutting them...
It really shocked me...
when Young Ji messaged me and said...
I was just talking.
Young Ji, when did you say you wanted to make rice cakes?
I want to make 100,000 dollars or even 1 million dollars.
I want to make rice cakes from scratch.
I even want to start a fire with tinder.
But you told me...
Don't take everything I say literally.
Since when did you start believing everything I say?
Please understand her. She's being delirious...
- from exhaustion.
- This is seriously hard work.
Everyone says fresh rice cakes taste the best.
Young Ji will do it, but...
(Screaming)
Please understand her.
Who said I wanted to make rice cakes myself?
Who said I wanted to do it?
I just wanted to do the cool part at the end of slicing it.
Who said I wanted to make baekseolgi...
and grind the rice into flour?
(The head chef finally unleashes her winning rant.)
- We can do it.
- Get rid of all these machines.
But if anyone leaves even one rice cake behind...
Do you really think I won't chase them down?
Don't you dare leave a single rice cake.
Yu Jin, write down the names of everyone who leaves rice cakes.
Put them on the blacklist.
Okay.
(After calming down, it's time to make jeolpyeon.)
(While Young Ji is still ranting)
- Nice.
- Could you stick it in once?
- How did it turn out?
- It looks good.
- It turned out well.
It's perfect.
(Switching to the jeolpyeon nozzle)
It's done.
- Adjust it to jeolpyeon?
- It's done.
I can't wait to find out.
(A cute little piece of jeolpyeon peeks out.)
Thanks to you, it's coming out fast and smoothly.
Eun Ji, it's perfect.
- It looks incredible.
- Eun Ji, you're doing well.
It's amazing.
(Fuelled by compliments, she works even harder.)
(It's nice and plump.)
- Look how fat it is.
- Yes.
This is good.
- All the ingredients are in.
- Nice.
Young Ji, it looks so pretty.
(Perfectly shaped jeolpyeon)
- It came out really nicely.
- I can't believe it.
- Unbelievable.
- Nice.
- We did a great job.
- I agree.
Take photos. It looks beautiful.
Eun Ji, you're the best.
Let me know when you're ready to learn how to clean that.
- What?
- How to clean it.
(Cleaning is the foundation of cooking.)
Peeling this off is...
- oddly satisfying.
- I know.
I'm sorry for saying I wanted to make rice cakes.
I didn't mean it literally.
I didn't expect anyone to listen to me.
I sincerely apologise.
We can do it. We'll help you.
Will you help me?
- We can do it.
- Can you really do it?
Hey, GG!
(Singing)
(Shall we start?)
(Oh, my. Look at her)
- Head Chef, keep working.
- Okay.
(Okay...)
- Yu Jin.
- Yes?
How are you doing?
The sink is really low.
- Okay.
- It's too low.
Do you want a step stool?
No, it's okay.
Eun Ji, the weather is beautiful today.
- Yes.
- I hope that it doesn't rain.
(Scrubbing)
This reminds me of my old part-time job.
Making rice cakes takes...
more people than I thought.
(With this many tools to clean)
So this is what running a business is like.
(Cleaning up is just as much work as making the rice cakes.)
Yu Jin, hold on.
Do we have to clean all this every single day?
(That's right...)
It's because we aren't the head chef.
- That's why...
- But...
we're the ones doing it.
Making rice cakes is no joke.
- Maybe that's why they're so good.
- Right.
Korean rice cakes deserve...
way more recognition.
Cooking shows are exhausting on a whole different level.
- We haven't even started cooking.
- Right.
Exactly.
Thinking about doing this every single day...
Huge respect to everyone who runs their own business.
Maybe it's hard because it's our first day.
If we get used to it tomorrow...
Never mind.
Our business is over for today.
We haven't even cooked anything yet. I'm terrified.
- Let's eat together.
- Let's gather.
- Gather up, everyone.
- Gosh.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you for the food.
- It's delicious.
The view is incredible.
(They have been stuck in the kitchen all day, but...)
(Space Rice Cake sits in front of a breathtaking ocean view.)
This dried laver is excellent.
- I like the dried laver too.
- Yes.
It's delicious.
I guess there's always room for food.
- We must eat to survive.
- We worked hard, after all.
Right.
All we did was run the rice cake dough through the machine.
(Already wiped out after running the dough through the machine)
It's the quietest variety show we've ever done.
It's practically white noise at this point.
On "Earth Arcade," the harder it was,
the bigger the success was.
How successful will this be?
- How much harder...
- What if no one watches it?
(We want to succeed.)
That's so funny.
I'm full.
Are you full?
- Yes.
- Me too.
Really?
(Current Time: 3pm)
We'll be doing a soft opening.
- Oh, no.
- A soft opening.
- Is it like a practice service?
- Yes.
(A final check before the opening)
- First, we need a name.
- Yes.
We need to name our place.
For now, let's just call it "Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki."
- For now.
- "Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki."
This is its pseudonym,
"Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki."
Originally, I wanted to call it, "Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki."
"Don't eat ghost pepper tteokbokki, it's a challenge."
Can you all do that?
- Come on, Eun Ji.
- You need a working title.
"Challenge: Beat Lee Young Ji."
- Right.
- "Challenge: Beat Lee Young Ji."
"Don't eat ghost pepper tteokbokki, it's a challenge."
Well done.
- And pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Pollack roe...
- Pollack roe and clam pasta.
It's tiramisu, but it has chestnuts and rice cake.
How about "Chestnut Tyranno?"
Chestnut Tyranno!
(The comedian version of "Chestnut Tyranno")
(A dinosaur from the Cretaceous appears in Goheung.)
Like the dinosaur.
(Confidence is half the recipe when naming dishes.)
Like a Tyrannosaurus.
- I like this idea.
- Isn't it nice?
We'll name it Chestnut Tyranno.
Don't be ridiculous.
It's just a working title.
A working title.
Yes, as a working title.
You can say it like this. "Chestnut Tyranno."
- "Chestnut Tyranno."
- How about...
(Chestnutericano)
(Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki, pollack roe and clam pasta...)
(The soft opening menu is complete.)
- Here we go.
- Okay.
(The preparation starts.)
This is...
the perfect amount of consistency.
(The head chef is making her signature sauce.)
Is this enough for today?
Yes, that's perfect.
I chopped them well, right?
Mimi is the best.
(The sous-chef preps the ingredients with love.)
(Encouraged by the compliment, she chops away even harder.)
I'll check on the rice cakes.
I look like So Ji Sub today, and I like it.
(Ji Sub falls silent.)
Eun Ji, the rice cakes...
What's wrong?
- My goodness.
- What's the matter?
They're stuck to the plastic.
Goodness.
No, take them off slowly.
(Now we have another problem sticking to us.)
(The rice cakes still refuse to cooperate.)
I'm worried about the baekseolgi.
(The baekseolgi...)
This can't be helped.
(Sighing)
- Are you okay?
- What kind of sound was that?
- Everything depends on running...
- The rice cake...
the rice cake through the machine properly.
Who would've thought...
we'd be making rice cakes ourselves?
(No one saw it coming.)
Who suggested making rice cakes from scratch anyway?
(Crying)
Since when did you start taking everything I say so seriously?
It's because you're the head chef.
(Reconsidering what it really means to be the head chef)
Chef.
- You became awfully quiet.
- What?
These rice cakes are being so annoying.
(It's because the rice cakes are annoying.)
I told you. We should've just bought them.
(Sighing)
(Laughing)
I'm sorry. It's my bad.
Why isn't it coming out?
(The staff's frustration keeps piling up.)
This brat...
(She's not cursing.)
Can someone post a job listing for a part-timer?
Maybe on some secondhand marketplace.
Director, instead of giving us feedback,
get in here.
(Even the youngest tries to keep smiling.)
My goodness.
(Even the skies are against them.)
Are you okay?
Mimi, do you need help?
(Even the trusted sous-chef)
It's not open.
Wait a minute.
What if people watching this show think...
that we're idiots?
- My gosh, look at this.
- Here we go.
- One, two, three.
(The preparation is complete.)
(Exhausted)
I'm only checking my phone now.
I looked at it at noon. I look at it after five hours.
- What time is it?
- It's 5:52pm.
- Don't talk to me anymore.
- Okay.
Hey, ladies.
- Yes?
- Can we do this once?
- It's 5:52pm.
- Where we seat our customers...
Ladies, what are you doing?
What's the problem?
Ladies, could you get up for a minute?
We still have eight minutes.
Let's just check where we'll seat our customers.
- That's the only...
- You're such an MZ kid.
Shouldn't we figure out where to seat our customers?
- Okay, I'll read the vibe.
- The vibe?
Okay.
Don't read the vibe and get moving
- She's really bossy.
- Is there no medium size?
She told me not to sell the medium size.
Boss.
- Boss.
- Yes?
If you keep treating me like this, I'll quit.
- Boss, who else would work here...
- You know what?
- besides us?
- She's right.
Go ahead and quit.
Report me to the labour office.
- Listen, boss.
- I'll post you on Instagram.
"Darn it."
"That MZ part-timer totally ruined my day."
- I can post too.
- Go ahead.
- Me too.
- "Darn it."
"My boss has lost it."
"Darn it, my part-timer has lost it."
- We can do it too.
- Okay, bring it on.
- These days...
- Goodness.
- It's not easy.
- Let's see who backs down first.
Just scrap the whole thing.
(The soft opening begins.)
(On today's menu)
(Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki)
(Simmered for 10 minutes in our handmade sauce)
(Thick garaetteok)
(Topped with an assortment of fried seafood)
(Next is Young Ji's dish made with pride and joy)
(Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, It's a Challenge)
(Beat Lee Young Ji)
(The challenge menu that brings extreme spiciness)
(Next is Sous-chef Mimi's signature dish.)
(Pollack roe and clam pasta)
(Refreshing clam...)
(and thinly sliced jeolpyeon)
(Creating a fantastic taste with pollack roe)
(As for dessert, it's Chestnut Tyranno.)
(Sweet chestnut cream...)
(topped with a snowfall of roasted chestnut powder)
(Finished with a whole chestnut)
(It's served with...)
(your choice of 2 slushies, pomegranate or coffee.)
Come on, family. Let's go in.
(A mysterious family enters.)
- Today, I will...
- Dad.
- Is anyone there?
- Yes.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Is it a tteokbokki place?
That's right.
- Welcome.
- That's why we're here.
- Hello.
(Buzzing with chatter)
- They're here.
Stay focused.
- Figure out the number of people...
- by listening.
- We stopped by.
- It's Director Yeong Seok.
- What? No way.
(It's Director Yeong Seok.)
It's Director Yeong Seok.
(They look very familiar, but today, they're customers.)
I can't understand the menu.
Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Ma'am?
- Yes, I'm coming.
- Excuse me.
- "Yes, I'm coming."
(After one day, she mastered the customer service tone.)
Did you call me?
You don't even come when we call you. Why are you so slow?
If you're in such a hurry, you should've come yesterday.
- Here's some dongchimi.
- Yesterday?
- Thank you.
- What's this?
This is dongchimi that we serve you on the side.
- It's yuzu dongchimi.
- I see.
- This looks good.
- Yes.
- By the way...
- Yes?
I don't understand the menu at all.
- Can you explain it to us?
- Sure.
Chestnut Tyranno!
(Laughing)
(The meat lover performance attempt was too hasty.)
That startled me.
(Retreating behind a tree)
What did you say?
Could you do it again? What is this?
Chestnut Tyranno!
(Crying)
- Chestnut Tyranno is...
- What kind of dish is it?
Chestnut Tyranno is...
tiramisu made with chestnut cream.
We reimagined it using rice cakes.
That's Chestnut Tyranno.
What does this mean?
Challenge! Beat Lee Young Ji, 175cm Tall.
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, It's a Challenge.
Is that the whole name?
- This tteokbokki is...
- Yes.
basically a challenge tteokbokki.
It's made with ghost peppers,
the world's hottest pepper.
It's extremely spicy, and the portion is quite big.
It contains 175cm of rice cake.
Is it okay for four of us to eat?
Our food is always good.
(Approaching slowly)
- Also, - I guarantee it.
if you complete the challenge,
you'll get a photo.
- We will also give you a pot.
- A pot?
But it's not just any pot.
It's a signed pot.
A pot signed by a famous celebrity.
We have many pots at home, so...
Hurry up and order, please!
(Scolding)
(Oh, I'm sorry.)
(I was just getting nervous.)
- We got an order.
- Okay.
- Lee Young Ji, medium.
- Is it the standard size?
One pollack roe and clam pasta.
Two Chestnut Tyranno.
One challenge tteokbokki. That's all.
That's crazy.
They ordered a lot.
- Okay.
All right.
(It's coming right up. We'll make it delicious.)
Is this a library?
- No one is saying a word.
- No one?
They're completely focused.
(Silence)
(They're not studying.)
(They're making tteokbokki.)
One, two, three, four, five.
(They're making fried food.)
(Stifling a laugh)
What do you need?
This serious atmosphere...
(Serious Chef Kim Mi Hyun...)
(and Mr. Pollack Roe and Clam Pasta)
This is me.
- Is it you?
- This is Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki.
Nice.
(The dishes are ready.)
Excuse me.
I was saying...
(Here's your order.)
This is your...
- Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki.
- My gosh.
This is pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Pollack roe and clam pasta?
- Yes.
- I'll put it in the center.
- My goodness.
(Challenge! Beat Lee Young Ji, 175cm Tall)
- What's this?
- It's the dessert.
This is Chestnut Tyranno.
- Gosh, this is...
- Oh, my.
It looks amazing.
(Taking a bite of the fried food first)
She's running away.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
There's a bone in it.
- It's a fish bone.
- What if it got stuck in my throat?
I almost died.
- How could you...
- What do we do?
- Eun Ji.
- What's the matter?
They want compensation because they found a bone.
Hold on.
Hello, I'm the manager here.
Didn't we see her a moment ago?
I apologise.
Since we fillet everything ourselves 1 by 1,
we must have missed one.
I sincerely apologise again.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
I apologise.
We'll be more careful next time.
I'm sorry, and I'll give you today's drink...
- on the house.
- Thank you.
I apologise.
A bone like this is fine.
- May I take your plate?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Let me know if you need anything.
(Clapping)
- Is it solved? Oh, my.
- It's okay.
Difficult customers like them...
(They're about to start eating.)
I've been curious about this the most. I haven't had it before.
(Tasting tteokbokki that she made)
(One bite for Yu Jin who worked hard)
- It's full of cheese.
- Right?
- Isn't the sauce good?
- Yes.
This is really good.
- Actually, this...
- I never had it before.
The texture...
of the rice cake is too cheesy.
But the sauce is delicious.
I agree.
(Next is pollack roe and clam pasta made by the sous-chef.)
What goes in it...
Good?
It's so good.
(The pollack roe and clam pasta is flawless.)
(Yeong Seok tastes the Chestnut Tyranno.)
- Is it supposed to taste like this?
- This...
- By the way, - Oh, that?
the rice cakes came out too thick today,
and the cream is too runny.
But the flavour itself is right.
The portion is way too big.
- Right?
- Yes.
- You need to cut it down.
- Isn't it delicious?
If we can solve the rice cake issue,
- everything else will go smoothly.
- Right.
We'll have a discussion with the main office.
- Chestnut Tyranno.
- I tried it, and it was amazing.
We can reduce the portion dramatically.
- I agree.
- That's my personal opinion.
The customers would have eaten...
- a lot of carbs.
- Right.
- By the way, - Yes?
- are we locking in...
- The name is a little...
- the name "Chestnut Tyranno?"
- I know.
By hearing the name, people should know what it is.
It should include both rice cake and tiramisu.
Rice cake? The chestnut...
How about "tteokramisu chestnut?"
That sounds good.
- It sounds good.
- Doesn't it?
It's not...
- It's not bad.
- It's not bad?
- Tteokramisu chestnut.
- I admit that I like it.
- I like it.
- But we'll write it like this.
I like it.
- That's not bad.
- Like this.
- That looks good.
- "Tteokramisu chestnut."
And let's add spacing too.
What did you think about the challenge tteokbokki?
- So...
- That one?
It was really good,
but it's a shame that people can only try it...
- if they do the challenge.
- It's a shame.
Let's make Lee Young Ji Tteokbokki...
- with mala sauce.
- Mala sauce.
And another one to resolve Young Ji's resentment.
We need an intense challenge...
that people are dying to do.
- Intense enough for Instagram.
- Something for Reels.
What is it called? Ghost popper?
- Ghost pepper.
"While eating ghost pepper tteokbokki,"
"your lips will swell."
How about something like that?
How about "Tteokbokki That Takes You to the Sky?"
- Is there any pretty phrase?
- How about...
Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.
- It's Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.
- That sounds great.
It's so spicy...
- that it sends you to the sky.
- By the way...
(As a challenge dish, it's extremely spicy.)
(Made with 175cm of rice cake)
(A more approachable version of mala tteokbokki)
(The rice cake is 85cm, half of Young Ji's size.)
- What else?
- Let's just keep...
coffee and pomegranate slushies.
The name "coffee slushy" is...
- a little disappointing.
- Right?
Is there another word for "slushy?"
Icy coffee.
- Icy sounds good.
- Icy coffee.
- What?
- Cheap coffee.
(Drinking cheap coffee)
What's the opposite of cheap?
- Expensive.
- Goguryeo.
How about Goguryeo Coffee?
No way.
It's not cheap coffee, but fancy...
How about Goguryeo Coffee?
Fancy...
- Fancy coffee slushy.
- Fancy.
What about the pomegranate slushy?
Crunchy pomegranate slushy.
(Just pushing through with confidence)
- "Crunchy?"
- How about "zesty?"
- "Zesty" sounds good.
- Zesty.
(Fancy coffee slushy)
(Zesty pomegranate slushy)
(The menu is complete.)
Hello. Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
(Their business hasn't even opened yet,)
(but today was a very long day.)
That must be it.
- It's our lodging.
- We're here.
The problem is...
how we'll run the rice cake dough through the machine tomorrow.
How will we make the rice cakes tomorrow?
That machine is unbelievably delicate.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
I'm so scared for tomorrow. I'm an anxious type of head chef.
(She's worrying about herself.)
I'm about to lose it. Actually, I'm terrified.
(The night filled with anxiety comes to an end.)
(The morning of opening day finally arrived.)
(As if celebrating the grand opening,)
(today's weather is gloomy.)
(On a day like this,)
(will anyone come?)
(Early morning at the accommodation)
- Hello.
- Young Ji.
- You put on your makeup.
- I did.
Gosh, it's raining.
- Hello.
- I'm coming down with something.
(The truth is, last night...)
Running a business requires so much preparation.
Can anyone keep up...
- with this schedule?
- How many times did we do this?
This chestnut cream is killing me.
Why does the day feel so long?
(The Earth Arcaders were occupied throughout the day.)
- Did you get some sleep?
- What?
I woke up once at 3am, 4am, 5am, and 6am.
You woke up every single hour?
When I woke up at 3am, I thought that it was 6am.
- Did you sleep well?
- You look beautiful today.
- Do I look cute?
If I sprint from here to there at full speed,
would it take about a minute and a half?
- Try it.
- Try it, Young Ji.
No, don't.
Young Ji, don't waste your energy. We have a lot to do.
- Young Ji...
- You guys are terrible.
Please calm down.
- We're almost there.
- Gosh.
- What's the matter?
- It really hurts.
Are you pretending to be hurt to avoid going to work?
(Groaning)
- I don't think I can go to work.
- Stop it.
We're at work. I feel so good.
Young Ji, go in already.
I don't want to work.
(Arriving at work feeling lighthearted)
When it's raining
(Now it's time to prep.)
And the music is playing
Everyone, put on your aprons and get to your stations.
- I forgot my apron.
- What?
- I forgot my apron. I'll run home.
- Me too.
(So it began 30 seconds after arriving at work.)
(A self-chase mission to find the apron)
(A joke came back to haunt her.)
Why didn't you...
bring your apron?
(Panting)
I don't want to run this business anymore.
(Her true feelings)
(Sprinting of anger)
(The aprons are safely rescued.)
I'm unbelievably happy.
I'm so happy...
that I could go for a bottle of soju.
It's raining. Wait a minute.
What are we going to do if it rains today?
Let me think before I start running again.
I need to hurry and prep the ingredients.
The rice cakes go into the steamer.
How do you turn on that machine again?
(It's called the rice cake shaper.)
I can't even run that fast.
Director, please don't abandon me.
Director!
Where are you going?
(Everyone fends for themselves.)
(Thankfully, they arrived together.)
(It's time to run the dough through the machine.)
Hey, rice cake shaper!
Hey you, rice cake shaper.
What are you doing here?
Are you good at pounding?
(Intrigued)
Are you good at pounding rice cakes?
Hey, rice cake shaper.
We need to get the first step right. It's making the rice cakes.
Right.
If the rice cake is off,
- everything else is off too.
- Even when we make tiramisu.
Nothing ever turns out perfectly.
- The rice cakes are very important.
- Right.
Thank you.
(First, they wash their hands thoroughly.)
- Flour team, prepare the flour.
- Yes, chef.
Don't we have to rinse it?
We need to drain out the water.
It got heavier after sitting overnight.
Relax your arms. Don't strain yourself.
Don't we just have to carry it?
You're right. One, two, three.
(Splash)
I feel a little foolish.
(A task that didn't need to happen in the yard)
Let's go.
- Do we leave this here?
- I'll take it later.
(Chuckling)
We look a little ridiculous right now.
It'll get edited out anyway.
(The service team's challenging future is ahead.)
Pour it all. One, two, three.
(All into the rice grinder)
Eun Ji, there's a lot.
Here we go.
(The power is on.)
- Let's go, Eun Ji.
- You can do it.
- Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
Who are we?
- Earth Arcaders.
- We can do everything.
- We can do it.
There's nothing we can't do.
(Mixing after adding water and salt)
- It shouldn't clump up, right?
- Right.
Won't it be strained anyway?
Yesterday, it was okay as long as it clumped a little.
When the rice grinder is done, shouldn't it make a noise?
(Once the service team grinds the rice)
- Please spread it out flat.
- Okay.
Next is the rice cake shaper.
Turn on the rice cake shaper.
- Be careful.
- Safety first.
- Watch out behind you.
Your body is your most valuable asset.
(The steamer starts.)
(A refreshing blast of steam pours out.)
- Chef, do we need more?
- What?
Should we make more?
Please take a look at the amount.
(While Mimi spreads out the rice flour)
Three of these for baekseolgi.
(While Yu Jin weighs the salt)
(While the head chef washes the cloth)
Shouldn't we put in more? It should be 1cm...
- Young Ji, can I use this?
- Chef, do we need to put in more?
- Young Ji, this...
- Wait, what?
Young Ji, you forgot to do one thing. Think carefully.
- What?
- You forgot to do one thing.
(Find what's wrong with this picture)
What?
(Completely innocent)
The whole room is getting foggy right now.
You didn't turn on the exhaust hood.
- Oh, right.
- Turn on the ventilation fan.
- That's good.
- I'm sorry, everyone.
It's okay.
I thought I saw a mountain spirit.
It's a humidifier.
It's nice and moist in here.
(Giggling)
It's okay. We didn't start a fire.
- Do we need three of these?
- This is big.
What?
(Acting strange to hide the embarrassment)
What? Didn't someone talk to me?
(Finally placing the steaming tray on the steamer)
- Once the steam builds up...
- I see.
- My gosh.
- Okay, that was nice.
- I got it now.
- That's good.
(20 minutes later)
Do it slowly.
(Gosh, it's hot.)
It's hot.
Be careful.
- Oh, my.
- This is done.
(Checking the baekseolgi)
If it's too thin, we'll build three layers.
- Okay, for now...
- Let's keep going.
We already made it.
(Checking with the main team)
You just made a big hole in it.
Let it cool for now.
If you keep poking at it, it'll eventually come out.
She said, "If you keep poking at it, it'll eventually come out."
(She's right.)
When you go get groceries, please buy some eggs.
And some rice.
- You mean, microwavable rice?
- Yes. Thank you.
- We're going to the market.
- See you later.
- Be careful.
- Drive safely.
Be careful.
Stay strong.
What should we do now, Mimi?
- Let's drink some water.
- We should keep it clean.
Now the real battle begins.
We have to finish making rice cakes before they come back at 10am.
(Meanwhile, the shopping team heads to the supermarket.)
Gosh, it's pouring.
I'm glad that there aren't many cars at this time.
I know.
There's H Mart. Is that a farmers' market?
This is the downtown area. There's a karaoke bar called Venus.
Eun Ji, there's a cafe.
(They're beyond excited for their first outing.)
There's a convenience store.
The supermarket is big.
(They arrive at the supermarket.)
- Yu Jin, what should we buy first?
- Over here...
I don't think we need vegetables.
- Vegetables? Eggs.
- Eggs.
Let's head over to the fresh food and dairy section.
We might as well buy an entire tray, right?
- It will take one month anyway.
- Right. They don't go bad easily.
Yu Jin, I'll bring the microwavable rice. Stay here.
(They also buy microwavable rice.)
(Grocery list: Eggs, microwavable rice)
There should be beef loin in the frozen food section.
- You're right.
- Shall we get it there?
(They buy shaved pork belly instead of beef loin.)
Eun Ji, I found headscarves.
- Headscarves?
- Headscarves.
- We need to buy headscarves.
- Young Ji needs a headscarf.
- Two headscarves.
- Which colours should we get?
- The leopard print looks cute.
- Shall we get one leopard print?
- We need 1 of these.
- Let's get 1.
I'm sorry, but can I keep the leopard print?
Keep it.
(Smiling)
We got the headscarves.
What else can we buy here?
- We need kitchen scissors.
- Shall we get this?
- Yes.
Scissors.
(Everything on the supermarket list is purchased.)
(They have to head to the market to buy a big basin.)
- Take a look over here.
- Okay.
There are a lot of things here.
This is just like a fancy department store.
Eun Ji, this place is amazing.
- Yu Jin.
- I'm glad that we came shopping.
This is a fancy department store for us.
(They forget about grocery shopping and switch to shopping mode.)
- Look, Eun Ji.
- It's a strawberry.
- Yes, this is how it should be.
- Strawberry.
- I'll get the strawberry shape.
- I'll get the toast bread shape.
It's easier to scrub with.
- Like this?
- Like this.
I need a nail file.
- An eyebrow razor...
- And nail clippers.
- How about this?
- Who wants a tongue cleaner?
- I'll get one.
- It looks cute.
- Hygiene. What else?
- Maintaining hygiene.
I got so excited that I even threw my notebook.
- We need to go now.
- Let's go now.
Eun Ji, can't we get one?
- Let's buy one of the squishy toys.
- Can we?
- It's cute.
- Right? This is really...
It's a stress ball.
We need to keep our stress in check.
We really need this, Eun Ji.
For our mental health.
You agree with me, right?
You know how people say...
"A happy wife makes a happy home."
A happy chef in the kitchen...
makes a happy restaurant.
(Right on)
Okay. We're done here.
(Heading back with a heavy cart and a light wallet)
- We bought a lot of good stuff.
- Right. We bought a lot.
I got everything I wanted.
- We bought the scrubbers too.
- They really have everything there.
Hey, Yu Jin.
There's a lot of dishwashing items here.
We found another fancy department store.
- What should we do?
- I think we should visit there.
- Hello.
- Look at that, Eun Ji.
Yu Jin, this place is legendary.
- This is driving me crazy.
- We should've come here first.
Look, Yu Jin. We can sit here while doing the dishes.
Eun Ji.
I think we must buy this.
Go over there and try sitting on it.
How does it feel?
Will it be comfortable to sit there while doing the dishes?
Eun Ji, this is it.
Pretend you're doing the dishes and see how it feels.
(Pretending)
(She's posing perfectly as if she were doing the dishes.)
Was it inappropriate?
It's so good.
I really like it, Yu Jin.
Shall we get the largest, white one?
Please give us the largest one you have.
- This is...
- It's perfect.
- This is... Okay.
- It's perfect. Okay.
Where is it? I want to go check it out.
- Duwon-myeon.
- It's in Daejeon-ri.
- It's located by the sea.
- It's right by the sea.
- Daejeon-ri?
- Yes, Daejeon-ri.
- Yes.
- Daejeon-ri, Duwon-myeon?
- Please visit us soon.
- Okay.
- It's cold.
- Oh, dear. Eun Ji.
(They're done with grocery shopping!)
Let's start with jeolpyeon.
(Meanwhile, the kitchen team starts making rice cakes.)
Okay.
(Placing the baekseolgi that will transform into jeolpyeon)
- Hold on.
- I'll do it.
Look at that. It looks perfect.
(The baekseolgi is cooked to perfection.)
I'm glad we marked it earlier.
Here we go.
- Let's go.
- I'll...
I'll just do a quick test run and pull some out.
Okay.
(They get off to a smooth start, unexpectedly.)
(But...)
(The rice cake shaper won't even budge.)
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Director, why isn't this working?
- What's wrong?
- The rice cake won't come out.
(They hit a snag right from the beginning.)
Jebyeong, don't do this to us.
(She tries again calmly.)
- Oh, no. Stop.
- What is it?
Hold on. Stop the machine.
It's coming out from underneath.
Did something go wrong when we put it in?
Oh, you're right.
(Jeolpyeon is coming out squished from the wrong spot.)
It's coming out from underneath.
- I think we should reinstall it.
- Right.
(They struggle on their first try doing this on their own.)
This is driving me crazy.
- And then...
- Screw it in.
- Done.
- Okay. Let's try again.
- Done. Here we go.
- Here we go. I'll turn it on.
- Okay.
(The success of the business is on the line.)
- That's good. Great.
- It's working. What a relief.
Yes, that's good.
- Oh, gosh. I'll just pull it out.
- Pull it gently.
Okay. Go ahead.
- It's coming out nicely.
- Here we go.
I'm choked with emotion.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
I know, right?
I can't believe it's working.
I panicked.
- Okay. You can start stacking.
- It looks...
This is amazing.
- Young Ji, this is amazing.
- Good.
We're done with jeolpyeon.
- We're done with jeolpyeon.
- Yes, we're done.
- Garaetteok is a bigger challenge.
- I think I can stay positive.
That's good.
Nice. That's great.
Nice. Keep going.
(Stickiness, glossiness, thickness)
- This is crazy good.
- Nice. This is ridiculously good.
This is the best batch I've ever made.
- Great.
- I really did a good job.
(It looks like it came from a professional rice cake shop.)
This is insane.
(So garaetteok is piling up.)
Young Ji, this batch of garaetteok is just amazing.
Yes, that batch is amazing.
(They successfully made garaetteok as well.)
Look at this. It came out great.
Look here. One, two, three.
(She is touched.)
- Thank you.
- It came out really great.
Young Ji.
(But...)
(Raining)
Are you all right?
- It's raining. What do we do?
- Is this for real?
Mimi, it's pouring.
(It suddenly starts pouring.)
Are you all right?
- It's raining. What do we do?
- Is this for real?
Mimi, it's pouring.
(It suddenly starts pouring.)
Wait.
(The wind is blowing hard too.)
(Fluttering)
- I'm bringing water.
- Okay.
(The weather is looking ominous.)
(The rain and the wind are picking up.)
We haven't even opened our restaurant.
(The outdoor tables, before the restaurant is even open)
It's so humid today.
(It's humid in front of the restaurant.)
Oh, like this?
(The paper towel dreams of escaping.)
- Goodness. What's going on?
- I...
I lit a mosquito coil.
Should I light one more?
- The rice flour is...
- Oh, no.
- Are you all right?
- The wind is so strong.
- We will...
- Let's take a ten-minute break.
- Let's take a short break.
- Just for ten minutes.
- You two can go to your room...
- Okay.
- and rest for a while.
A screw fell out from the awning.
(The camera crew is packing up for now too.)
Mimi, stand there. I'll take a photo of you.
I just heard thunder.
- Young Ji.
- Mimi, say something, please.
- The rice cake we made...
- The kitchen is a mess now.
- Everything is...
- Guys, cover this...
- There's sauce or something in it.
- Oh, no. Gosh.
- Oh, goodness.
- Good.
Close the lid, at least. Yes.
Oh, no. Our kitchen is completely ruined.
Let's cover them with this.
(They cover the kitchenware with plastic sheet hastily.)
Who would come here for tteokbokki on a rainy day like this?
- Right. No one will come.
- That'd be crazy.
This is...
I'm so scared.
We might get an electric shock.
(They're worried about getting shocked on their grand opening day.)
This is our first day...
This is our first day here.
We just opened up the restaurant, and it's...
Look outside.
- Shall we go outside briefly?
- Okay.
- Just briefly?
Seriously.
I'm sorry.
Do you think anyone will come?
Will anyone come?
(Splashing)
No one can come in this rain.
I think our restaurant is doomed.
What should we do?
(The cloudy future)
We opened up a restaurant here!
Please come check it out!
Please come for tteokbokki!
Please come for tteokbokki.
We make our own rice cakes.
We made the rice cakes earlier today.
(Hollow eyes)
If it's just drizzling instead of pouring,
- we might have some customers.
- Exactly.
- I just heard thunder again.
- It's even thundering.
(Will they be able to open the restaurant today?)
- Then let's open it at 1pm.
- Okay.
We can take our time to prep everything.
- Let's have lunch too.
- Yes.
Let's drag it inside.
- Oh, I see.
- Let's move the whole thing.
(We are back, we are here)
(The food)
Gosh. Should we put this inside?
How should we do this efficiently?
(As the rain tapers off, they start preparing to open the restaurant.)
Let's put it aside.
(Meanwhile, these two are struggling to clean the rice cake machine.)
Gosh. Look at the rice cake wedged in here.
Seriously, rice cake...
(Filled with rice cake)
- It drives me crazy.
- Exactly.
Seriously, this is driving me crazy.
- But this... Wait. Eun Ji.
- Yes?
I think they made too many holes.
Why?
- I mean...
- We can't use this part.
- I'll go and complain about this.
- Right?
- We should complain about this.
- Hey.
We should complain about this.
Is there any way to prevent rice cake from being wedged?
- No. Right?
- No.
- Here...
- I can't complain to them.
- Okay. I'll do the rest.
- Right now...
They're already having a hard time.
- I can't say anything to them.
- Try shaking it.
(Watching them struggle touches a soft spot in their hearts.)
(Instead of complaining, they start cutting it out.)
This piece with a hole looks so funny.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You can do it.
The final quality all depends...
- on the condition of the rice cake.
- I know, right?
We must keep it clean.
(Pouring yuzu-based sauce over salted radish)
The dongchimi made on the 12th.
- Made on the 12th.
- I'm putting it in the fridge.
The dongchimi made on the 12th will be delicious. I love you.
You're amazing.
(It's heavy.)
Oh, gosh.
Darn it. This dongchimi is so heavy.
- Are you done with dongchimi?
- Yes, I'm done.
It's nice.
(Groaning)
(Shouting)
(Her tiredness fuelled her boisterousness.)
The development of civilization
The development of technology
I'm so glad I'm in charge of desserts.
We might've really had a fight if I was on the kitchen team.
It isn't easy.
You have about 40 minutes left.
How many servings should we prepare today?
About ten servings?
- Prepare ten servings? Okay.
- Yes.
Set it at 175cm.
If people order it, I'll use this.
If not, I'll cut it up.
It is an advanced strategy in a way.
The garaetteok is looking good today.
I have a good feeling about this.
You have a good feeling? That's nice.
The rice cakes are ready.
Pretty much.
It's getting thinner.
It's looking more like pasta, right?
This is some really good rice cake.
(She starts to make jeolpyeon noodles too.)
You need to pay us 1.3 dollars for every serving you had.
- Sorry?
- You need to pay us...
- one dollar thirty cents per dish.
- Was it per dish?
(What they mean by 1.3 dollars is...)
(Before the shop opened, when they'd earned nothing,)
(they bought ramyeon by putting it on the company tab.)
I don't understand.
You're supposed to pay the ingredient cost, anyway.
What is she saying, Chef?
- What's she saying?
- I don't know.
- What is it?
- They'll take 1.3 dollars...
for each ramyeon we had.
- I don't know.
- Ramyeon?
We...
We've yet to have any customers, so how can you say that?
You're taking 1.3 dollars from us.
- That's a complete rip-off.
- Exactly.
How can you even think of charging us so much?
I mean, I get it.
- They can take 1.3 dollars.
- Me too.
But why would they bring it up to us when we didn't get to sell anything?
(The powerless businesswoman is upset.)
We have no customers.
We didn't have a single team of customers.
Why would you bring it up now?
Please work!
Work, please!
We have so much to do!
(Current time: 12:52pm)
- You must be very stressed.
- This...
Eating sweet stuff when you're tired makes you happy.
I'll make this for you.
(Is this for me?)
(Yu Jin's efforts melt away in mere seconds.)
(I can't speak...)
(because I'm too stressed.)
How is it?
(She immediately drinks Yu Jin's love.)
You feel so much better, right? Isn't it tasty?
(Heck yes!)
(Humming)
It tastes so good iced.
- It's so good. I'm not lying.
- Mimi.
It's seriously good.
- I'm enjoying it.
- It's really sweet.
- It's so good.
- It tastes like latte, right?
It really tastes like latte.
Cafe latte.
- Guys.
- Please come out.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
Come out, everyone.
Okay.
Are you ready to greet enthusiastically...
and live happily?
Yes.
The nation-wide...
The nation-wide Space Rice Cake opens today.
Thankfully, the rain stopped right on time for the opening.
- The sky is helping us.
- I'm so glad.
- Honesty, humility, ahk.
- The sky is helping us.
As we shout out the cheer,
Yu Jin the youngest will flip this to "open."
Honesty.
- Humility.
- Ahk.
(Open)
Come and eat tteokbokki.
- Come and eat tteokbokki.
- Come over quickly.
- Buy rice cakes.
- Who wants tteokbokki?
- We've opened.
- Tteokbokki... There's no one.
- Please don't come.
- I don't know.
- Please don't come too early.
We're open now.
(Current time, 1pm)
(The first day of the business begins.)
- Let's do this.
(Determined, they wash their hands.)
Madams, sirs, please come!
Hello.
- We'll cook it nicely.
- Eat some tteokbokki.
Tteokbokki is so tasty.
This tteokbokki is amazing.
Where do they sell it?
Which restaurant is this tteokbokki from?
Which restaurant is this from?
Tteokbokki is so tasty.
Yu Jin, isn't the tteokbokki here really good?
Tteokbokki is so good.
It's so delicious.
Pollack roe and clam pasta? Like rock star?
- Pollack roe and clam pasta.
(They shout as loudly as they can, but there's no one around.)
Shall we leave the gate open?
Maybe that'll encourage people to walk in.
We should leave the gate open to invite them in.
(Wide open)
People might think we're not open.
The streets are so empty.
Why is it so quiet?
This is bad. What do we do if there are no people?
(Pacing around nonstop)
- It can't be this empty.
- Eun Ji.
Yes?
There's no one.
I sighted one grandma on the rooftop...
of the house all the way over there.
(Both Eun Ji and Yu Jin's efforts are fruitless.)
Far away.
I'll just leisurely cut rice cakes.
Okay. Make some spares.
I should cut now when I have the time.
Then I'll read the recipe calmly.
This is driving me mad.
- We made rice cakes in the morning.
- Can this even be aired?
What if nobody comes?
What should we do?
I'm just so scared.
- About what?
- This situation.
What's really scary is that we haven't even started.
What's really scary is having to throw away...
all the rice cakes we've made today.
Young Ji, let's go live on Instagram.
Let's go live on Instagram.
Post a story.
Do a live.
Do what?
- A live on Instagram.
- Start it now.
- Me?
- Yes.
There's nobody within a 500m radius.
I like the vibe here. Let me take you pictures.
Try walking further out. The raw fish restaurant owner or...
- That'll be rude.
- Is it?
This is a nice spot.
- Can you take pictures of me?
- Okay.
- You can take it for me.
- Thank you.
- This is insane.
The village chief didn't keep his promise.
A verbal agreement is still an agreement.
Why won't he uphold it?
I thought he was coming.
He's not. He isn't around.
Did you go look for him?
Click.
They're taking pictures here, Mimi.
- Mimi, they're taking pictures.
- Two, three.
What am I going to do with this spoiled brat?
- It's break time.
- She...
No, it's not. It's business hours!
Sorry.
Why are you doing this? I quit.
Is your concept for this season not a cute idol singer...
but a thoughtless one?
How can you say that?
- I quit.
- Are you Goguryeo?
- Eun Ji, I quit.
- Again.
- Do it again.
- Do what?
Pose again.
I'm taking a video. Take screenshots of it later.
- Hold on.
- Take screenshots.
- I'm so shocked.
- Look here.
Not having any customers is shocking as is,
- but the servers...
The servers are acting like this.
- Eun Ji, come here.
- Hold on.
I'm so shocked. Excuse me, Mimi.
I'm so shocked.
We sell tteokbokki.
Come and have tteokbokki.
There's nobody around.
There's nobody at all.
(Young Ji talks alone, and Young Ji listens alone.)
Eun Ji, Young Ji called me a thoughtless idol singer.
(Once the boss leaves, they start talking behind her.)
Is this right?
Can the head chef speak so rudely?
- Eun Ji. I'm sad.
- Mimi.
- Honestly... I'm sorry, - It's so...
but can you stop obsessing over rice cakes?
There's nobody around.
How can you focus solely on the business?
I'm telling you, we're not ready.
Only six servings are ready.
Nobody has come, Mimi.
Why're you so obsessed...
- with jeolpyeon?
- This is...
I'm starting to get scared now.
One is obsessed, and the other speaks rudely.
- What's with the kitchen team?
- Being in the kitchen is tough.
You can't work in the kitchen if you're sane.
So I'm saying...
Sous-chef, I don't think this is right.
- What do you mean?
- The head chef...
keeps changing the menus on her whim...
and coming up with concepts...
She called me thoughtless.
- A thoughtless idol singer.
- Yes.
It's because...
she isn't yet aware of how the world works.
Aren't you being too kind?
- Let's badmouth her together.
- Exactly.
Are you guys on the same team?
That's right.
- What about us?
We're on the same team. We are the world.
(We are the world)
- Yes, we are...
- We are the children
We are the world,
but I'm so upset.
What should we do, then?
Let's all rise up.
(They go on strike.)
Get out before she comes back.
- She's outside.
Hide here.
Come this way.
(Come this way!)
(They escape to the hall to avoid the roaming boss.)
Come here.
(A car passes by at that moment.)
Come and eat tteokbokki.
(She promotes the restaurant with an awkward smile.)
Come on!
He's so annoying.
I'm so mad.
She's here.
(Erasing her trace)
- What's this?
- She's here.
(Sighing)
What's this?
Where did they go?
Where...
(She sets off to find the employees.)
- This is...
- Right?
- Yes.
- The business isn't doing well.
When will we...
The business isn't doing well,
she speaks so rudely,
and she hasn't paid us the wages yet.
She called her a thoughtless idol.
We prepared for seven hours.
- But there are no customers.
- We can't take pictures freely.
I can't take pictures freely when I'm an idol singer.
People, guys.
Ma'ams.
What is it?
- What are you doing?
- We're upset.
We won't work.
(Upset)
(The employees successfully teased the owner.)
She's upset.
(The owner's insides are burning.)
Come and have tteokbokki!
All she cares about is the business.
That's all she cares about.
All Mimi cares about is jeolpyeon.
All she cares about is the business.
- We've lost. Let's go.
- Okay.
Goodness.
Eat tteokbokki...
Hello.
Tteokbokki...
(An old lady becomes curious about the young owner's shouts.)
Hello.
(She feels awkward now that she's actually talking with one.)
We're selling tteokbokki.
Would you like to eat tteokbokki...
(The local senior's gesture makes her feel hopeless.)
Eat tteokbokki!
(Polite)
Eat tteokbokki.
(Hesitating)
They're running away.
(Running away)
Tteokbokki...
(She's practically chasing away the customers at this point.)
I...
Switch off the drone.
It isn't the time for this.
Tteokbokki...
(Seniors, she doesn't bite!)
Apologise.
(Employee 1: Apologise!)
- You're the worst.
Why?
I can't work if I'm getting this kind of treatment.
What should I do?
I tried to hitch hike just now.
Tteokbokki hitch hike!
We shouted at a grandma on a rooftop to come here too.
But you spent...
seven hours to prepare,
and we were called...
thoughtless idol singer and comedian.
We don't want to work like this.
You scolded us for not working when we just took a few pictures.
Heavy is the crown, as they say!
I'm just so frustrated!
This is my first time doing business as well.
And the woman...
in the kitchen is completely obsessed...
with rice cakes!
- All Kim Mi Hyun does...
- Only rice cakes...
is cut the jeolpyeon.
She doesn't make rice cakes, she only cuts them.
We didn't get any order, and she's made 12 servings!
My talented individuals, I beg of you.
Please attract at least one customer.
How can you touch the floor with the gloves on?
Throw the gloves away.
(Even during the discussion, hygiene is important.)
(They had a dramatic breakthrough. And she threw away the gloves.)
- We're off.
- Good luck.
I believe in you, Lee Eun Ji!
The best comedian in Korea!
The winner of the Baeksang Arts Awards! Please.
Please attract customers.
- Wait here.
- This won't do.
We need sky dancers.
Everyone, it's so nice to meet you.
Space Ride Cake has opened.
The head chef makes...
great tteokbokki,
assisted by the sous-chef.
Come to Space Rice Cake!
- You need to repeat after me.
- Come!
(They're pretty serious about this.)
Yu Jin.
There are seniors.
Shall we do it over there?
Let's do it one more time over there.
When I say "come," you say "come."
- When I say "find," say "find."
- Find!
- When I say "love," say "love."
- Love!
It's a bit embarrassing. How will I do this?
- Yu Jin, step up here.
- Come on, Eun Ji.
Do it! Aren't you going to attract customers?
A car.
(Rushing)
A car is coming. Yu Jin, stand here.
(The employees get busy at the appearance of a luxury car.)
(They solemnly play a song.)
Are you ready... Put your hand on my shoulder.
Move your hips to the left first. Seven, eight.
Everyone, it's so nice to meet you.
We're Space Rice Cake.
Please show lots of love for the newly-opened restaurant!
Love!
Space Rice Cake has an amazing head chef.
Head chef is Lee Young Ji,
and Kim Mi Hyun makes desserts.
- Please support us!
- Support!
(Sure, good luck.)
Eun Ji, I said it was embarrassing.
Wait, who's laughing?
Don't mock us!
(She's very angry at the headquarter's mocking.)
Darn it.
Eun Ji.
Why didn't the word about our business spread?
Don't mock us.
- Mimi.
- Yes.
(While the salespeople are struggling)
- What are you doing?
- Cutting rice cakes.
- Boss.
- They're on strike.
- Head Chef.
- Yes.
Why do you get mad on your own...
and beg on your own?
We should teach the Gen Z a lesson.
I had to beg. Am I the strange one here?
I'm the head chef and the owner.
But I...
I just scolded them for taking pictures during the opening hours.
Am I the strange one? Am I the boomer?
Mimi, am I the strange one?
Stop cutting rice cakes and say something.
You're not Han Seok Bong.
Stop cutting rice cakes and speak. Am I the strange one?
They're slacking during working hours.
Am I wrong for telling them off?
They say I'm wrong and that I should apologise.
(The owner is so close to fainting from anger.)
They want me to apologise.
Catch them.
(Catch the employees.)
Let's go with this, then.
- Like this.
- Okay?
Don't stare too much at the raw fish restaurant.
(Aggressive promotion in front of the competitor)
Space Rice Cake has opened.
The rice cake is very delicious. Please show lots of love!
Love!
Ha!
Come on, Yu Jin.
Eun Ji.
I can't do this.
- Mimi...
- Yes?
Yes?
- Eun Ji!
- Why is she running away?
Why is she...
running away from me?
Mimi is still cutting rice cakes.
What? That woman is...
possessed by a rice cake spirit.
Wear your aprons. You must be cold.
- Love us.
- I love you guys.
- Put it on me.
- What kind of...
- What kind of idol singer am I?
- A sexy one.
(Satisfied with the compliment)
A sexy idol singer.
- And?
- A cute one.
A cute idol singer.
Gosh, those guys.
They're so ungrateful.
(Seok Bong's mother is frustrated too.)
This mess happened because the head chef left her post.
Don't you think?
- Mi Hyun.
- Come back and secure your spot!
I... Earlier, you told me to get the employees back.
What do you want me to do?
Is the head chef a punching bag?
What should I do?
Mimi, you told me to go and catch them.
What am I...
You're treating me like a head minion, not a head chef.
What's this?
Mimi, they say you're crazy.
They call you crazy for cutting rice cakes when there's no order.
- A human should be a bit crazy.
- Let's wash our feet outside.
Okay, let's.
And tear the recipe book.
There's no customer. What will we do?
I don't know.
Do you like rice cakes, ma'am?
(The salespeople are asking her a loaded question.)
- I do eat rice cakes.
- You do? Which is your favourite?
I like garaetteok.
- Would you like some garaetteok?
- Let me give you a taste of it.
- I'll bring it for you.
- Please wait. We'll bring it.
(Running to find garaetteok, which can be found so easily)
- Young Ji!
- Wrap it in dried gopchang laver.
(The old lady says something.)
You're coming to eat our food?
I'll go now if that's what you want.
No, a bit later.
Go take care of your business.
Come if you can.
Thank you.
- Young Ji.
- Yes.
We got a reservation.
(Out of office)
- Where are you, Young Ji?
- Where is she?
A reservation?
Go to the kitchen quickly!
Mimi, we got an order!
Goodness.
(She calls Seok Bong Mimi, who was taking a breather.)
We got a reservation. Let's go.
(They pick up the pace to the kitchen.)
What do you mean?
- See? They succeeded.
- What?
- Mi Hyun. Sous-chef.
Head Chef.
What she initially said was,
I'll go to taste it later.
So she made a reservation.
- Around what time?
- After she takes care of her stuff.
- Good job.
I really want us...
to work together to our best ability...
and show them what true tteokbokki is.
I agree.
- Now, the head chef...
- The master of tteokbokki.
- will work hard and well.
- Yes.
Apparently, ladies here like rice cakes.
- They like garaetteok.
- I'm glad to hear that.
So, to spread word among them,
can we have our garaetteok and dried gopchang laver...
- For tasting.
- for tasting?
- Sounds good.
- That sounds good.
When you serve dongchimi,
- I'll grill garaetteok slightly.
- That sounds good.
What should we do?
- Is there truly no way?
- We must do something.
The restaurant opposite sells raw fish.
- But they...
- It's an old lady.
She passed by just now too.
- Ma'am.
- This is her second round.
Come and have tteokbokki. Mimi.
- It sells raw fish.
- But they...
It's an old lady.
She passed by just now too.
- Ma'am.
- This is her second round.
Come and have tteokbokki.
- Mimi.
- Yes.
Gosh. There's an old lady.
(Yu Jin has found her too.)
There's an old lady.
Have some tteokbokki, ma'am.
Hello, ma'am.
- Ma'am.
- Ma'am, are you busy?
Hello.
(One on the right and one on the left)
We opened a new tteokbokki place.
(Closing in from both sides)
- Do you like tteok?
- I don't need it.
You should share it with good people.
- Goodness. This is...
Seniors love to have tteokbokki these days.
That's so nice of you to say.
- It's true.
- Please give it a try.
I'm embarrassed to go to such a fancy place.
- Someone like you should come...
- Please come.
- to make it shine.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- I'll escort you.
- It suits you...
- We'll welcome you.
perfectly.
It's really fancy inside.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
I'm touched by what you said, so I'm going to pay a visit.
(Mission accomplished!)
- Mimi!
- This way.
- She's cool.
- Ma'am.
(She goes straight to the store.)
Hold on. I'm suddenly nervous.
- She's on her own ride.
- Yes, she has her own ride.
Gosh. Thank you.
This way, ma'am.
(Finally, they have their first customer!)
Have a seat right here.
- I'll wash my feet first.
- Sure.
We'll be waiting.
These young ones are so persistent.
(We'll see you in a bit.)
(In the meantime,)
(a car parks in front of the store.)
- What?
- We'll persuade with flavours...
- once they're here.
- Hey.
They seem like young customers.
- Can you feel it?
- Yes.
Come and have some tteokbokki.
He's the village chief.
Hello, sir.
Are you the village chief?
- Hello, sir.
- Are you cooking right now?
- Yes, we're open.
- We're cooking.
- Pardon?
- We're open.
- Hello.
- Yes.
- Come inside.
- This way, please.
Please come inside.
(The village chief has come with his nephew.)
You're our first customers.
Gosh. There are many seats.
- Yes, that's right.
- Welcome.
You can step inside, sir.
Hold on. Are there two of you?
No. More are coming.
- More? Like how many?
- They'll come when I call them.
- Gosh. We really appreciate it.
- Sure.
Should I call some people?
(Should I call some people?)
We would greatly appreciate it.
- Yes?
- We would greatly appreciate it.
- Really?
- Let's go inside first.
You can recommend this place if it's worth recommending.
Make yourselves comfortable.
(They successfully seated them this time.)
Let's do this, Mimi.
Let's do this.
We're the best cooking duo in Korea.
We should get this ready since we've got customers.
Lay down the dried laver. Where is the dried laver?
Mimi, you need to prepare more jeolpyeon.
Yes. It's good here.
Please cut it over there.
- Where?
- We're going to serve this.
- Right now?
- Yes.
We have customers here.
(And the customer from earlier is coming.)
(In short they're in an urgent situation.)
Do I go through here?
(Turning it off)
(Entering right away)
You're back, ma'am.
- Hello.
- Gosh. It's you, the village chief.
- I was going the other way, - Yes.
but these people said they'd serve me tteokbokki.
Gosh. Our first customers. This feels good.
(Washing hands again for no reason)
(Sitting together)
- Would you like to order?
- Yes.
We'll have one original tteokbokki.
- A small one.
- Hello? Yes.
Okay.
- Ghost... pepper?
- Yes.
What's that?
This tteokbokki has ghost peppers in it
- They are very spicy chilli peppers.
- I see.
It also has mala in it.
- We'll give it a try.
- Okay.
And pollack roe and clam... Is that pasta?
- Yes.
- Yes, that's right.
It's made with rice cake that is thin like pasta.
- We'll order those three.
- Okay.
This makes me really nervous.
- The time of waiting.
- It's not the other times.
This time is really scary.
(Laughing)
(They're about to lose their sanity together.)
I'm more nervous than I am before going onstage.
(8 years as a rapper, 1 day as a chef)
(12 years as a singer, 1 day as a chef)
- Eun Ji, what's the vibe like?
- Yes?
They're very laid back.
- Are they calm?
- Okay.
They're laid back and calm.
One thing worries me, though.
The village chief asked me,
"Do you need more customers?"
So, I said, "The more, the merrier."
He said, "Hold on." And he started making calls.
Really?
Come here quickly.
(It's 100 percent true.)
Meeting with the village chief yesterday...
- was a lucky move.
- That's right.
- That's for the better.
- I love it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- We have our 1st order.
- Our 1st order.
One small original tteokbokki,
One small one.
one ghost pepper-mala,
Ghost pepper-mala? It's a medium one, right?
and one pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. We can do this.
- We're moving.
- We are.
- We'll serve the original first.
- Okay.
The small one.
(The kitchen team starts prepping first.)
(The service team gets ready to serve.)
(When Yu Jin takes dongchimi out of the fridge,)
(Eun Ji puts it in a bowl right away.)
I'll serve the dongchimi.
I was going to serve it with the rice cake.
Okay. Let's do that.
(Bringing jeolpyeon right away)
This is yuzu dongchimi.
We make our own rice cakes here.
- Really?
- We made this rice cake today.
Please enjoy it with the dried laver.
Is this the first day of business?
Yes, you're our first customers.
- I see.
- Gosh. Why did you invite me?
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- It's yuzu dongchimi.
(They bought some time with dongchimi and jeolpyeon.)
Give it a try.
(At that moment, Head Chef is feeling super nervous.)
We'll serve the original first.
(The village chief's table: Small original tteokbokki, 1)
Okay.
(Adding green onions to the broth)
(Adding the special seasoning to it)
I'll show what I've got with the original tteokbokki.
Our first order.
Player Lee Young Ji is on the move.
I'll make it with care and love as it's for the customers.
(It's time to add fish cakes.)
- I'll add the rice cake...
- Yes.
- for the small original one.
- Okay.
(After adding garaetteok,)
Nice.
(she starts the timer for 10 minutes.)
(Mimi is coating ingredients in batter.)
Today, we'll serve two of each for the original one.
(Shrimp, cuttlefish, and cod are ready.)
Let me know when they'll have it.
(They'll be fried and served right away.)
(In the meantime,)
(the village chief keeps making calls...)
(to them.)
- Hello.
(The phone for the mission)
Right. Welcome.
- The village chief called you.
- Yes.
Come in.
Gosh. Both the head and the chief are here.
- Sit over here.
- Hello.
- This way?
- Yes.
The menu is up here.
(Their roles are reversed for some reason.)
Come.
(Staring)
(Our menu is a bit difficult.)
(Eun Ji will give a brief lecture on the menu.)
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, It's a Challenge.
(Eun Ji's hard work)
(Laughing)
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Pollack roe and clam pasta.
(Laughing)
What is she doing?
Now that's self-sacrifice.
Zesty pomegranate slushy.
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, It's a Challenge.
That's how she falls into a rut.
(Feeling sorry)
Thank you.
Ghost pepper.
(Eun Ji's menu lesson)
I'll have this one.
- You'll go with the original.
- This one.
- Medium size?
- Yes.
Okay. Medium size, it is.
(In the meantime, in the kitchen,)
(what is she doing?)
Are you all right?
- Is it okay to step inside?
- It was just...
Yes, you can come in.
- It's so scary.
- It's nothing.
(Actually, a special secret...)
(is hidden in Young Ji's tteokbokki.)
(It's time!)
It looks ready.
No. You shouldn't think that it's ready.
- Then it doesn't taste right.
- No.
I know what you're saying.
(For garaetteok to absorb the sauce,)
It'll be ready in ten minutes.
(it'll take 10 minutes!)
I'm excited to cook.
I'm happy. I love you all.
(Current progress of tteokbokki)
(Original: 50 percent, Mala: 0 percent)
Now, I'll make the ghost pepper tteokbokki.
(Only now, she starts to make the second dish.)
Did you hear we have an order of a medium original tteokbokki too?
I didn't hear about the additional order.
I'm hearing this for the first time.
- There's an additional order.
- Okay.
I feel good right now.
Who is this guy?
He's my nephew.
He's Mi Suk's son.
- You should've told me.
- What a handsome guy.
- He looks so much like her.
- He's handsome.
- So I was going to ask.
- Exactly.
He is such a good son.
- He's good-looking.
- Yes.
What is your mom doing?
She's coming.
- I see.
- We came separately.
(Actually, Mi Suk is coming right in.)
Welcome.
Yes. You can go inside.
There are customers here,
- so do you want to go to...
- Come in.
Is she your friend, sir? Please go inside.
The village chief is...
- amazing.
- Is he a superstar?
We have another table because of him.
- The village chief is awesome.
- He's amazing.
He is like...
George Clooney.
- That amazing?
- "Let's do it."
- Nice.
- Young Ji.
- It looks so good.
- It's really tasty.
(When the first tteokbokki starts to simmer,)
(she adds mini sausages right away.)
(When the fryer reaches the right temperature,)
Okay.
(shrimp, cod, and cuttlefish go in.)
I'm starting to fry them.
(After setting the timer,)
(she moves it up and down so that they don't stick together.)
- Let's go.
- Let's go. We can do it.
- Yes. Tteokbokki looks good today.
- Yes.
(Moving a long way to start making the pasta)
We'll get started quickly.
(She turns on the heat first.)
(She starts...)
(by adding minced garlic to olive oil.)
(After sautéing it for a while...)
Mimi, one minute left on the fryer.
- Okay.
- It's for one small original.
Okay.
(She goes back to finish the fritters.)
(She takes out the crunchy fritters.)
They look good.
I'll add the fritters now.
Okay. Add them.
(Cuttlefish)
(Shrimp)
(Cod)
(Lastly, she adds scallions...)
(and sesame seeds to finish.)
Eun Ji, a small original tteokbokki is ready to be served.
(Finishing in 10 minutes)
- Is it this one?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Here's the small original tteokbokki.
- Nice.
- Here it is.
(Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki, pollack roe and clam pasta)
Hurry and eat it.
It's big. Is it supposed to be served like this?
It's huge tteokbokki.
(The old lady tries a bite first.)
(And the village chief's family tries it too.)
Why aren't you eating that?
(Savouring)
It's tasty.
- Is it tasty?
- What?
- Yes, it's tasty.
- Does tteokbokki taste good?
Yes.
Goodness. This is so tasty too.
- This is tasty too.
- Dongchimi is tasty.
- Yes.
(Slurping)
(A mysterious shade appears in the meantime.)
It's good.
Goodness. This is so tasty too.
Do they find it tasty?
They said it was tasty.
Really? I'm happy to hear that.
- They said it was good.
- Thank you.
They say it's tasty.
That's nice.
(Reason: Ghost Paper Tteokbokki needs to be made ASAP)
(Adding chilli bean sauce to add the mala flavour)
I'll add 1.5 spoonfuls.
(Adding the spicy tang with the Sichuan pepper oil)
(Even the ghost pepper powder too!)
Seventeen minutes.
Garaetteok is added.
Okay.
(And she keeps simmering it down.)
(Something looks missing.)
(It's because...)
(it's missing the beef loin.)
(Remember me.)
(Current status of tteokbokki)
(Missing beef loin)
(But the chef hasn't realised it.)
Young Ji, what about the beef loin?
That's right.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
(Sighing)
(She looks for the beef loin in a hurry.)
This is crazy.
It's okay, Chef.
- I'm working on it.
- We have enough time.
It's okay.
(Finally adding the beef loin)
It's all good.
(While she tries to fix her mistake in a hurry,)
(another tteokbokki is left without the rice cake.)
- Is that...
- It's the original tteokbokki.
I see. The original.
They'll serve the same thing for us.
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki is ready.
Ghost Pepper is ready.
- Okay.
- Okay. I'm coming.
Come, Monkfish.
Good job. You're generous.
(Tteokbokki is simmering without rice cake.)
I'll take it.
- It's over here.
- I see.
(Current status of tteokbokki)
(Missing rice cakes)
Hello.
(Here comes the Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.)
(They make room on their table.)
- Here's the spicy one.
- It's...
Is it the mala one?
Why do you serve us only?
(Sadly, the tteokbokki is for the village chief's table.)
I didn't eat anything in the morning.
(She adds rice cake for the head of the women's association.)
- I added rice cake.
- Okay. Thank you.
(Now, it has to simmer for 10 minutes.)
(Rice cake has returned.)
- Why isn't ours coming?
- Right, sir.
(Right, sir.)
It's coming right away.
Our head chef is taking care of it all the time.
Please give us a minute.
Because it's our first day,
the head chef is all over the place.
We'll come back with it quickly.
- Okay.
- Yes.
People on Table Two said,
"Why isn't our food coming?"
- I see.
- Sorry.
I'll make it over here.
(The kitchen team is in chaos.)
- Yes.
- A comment from Table Two.
- I'll get on with it.
- Okay.
(The service team is stressed from both sides.)
(While Young Ji is in a hurry,)
(it'll take a while for it to simmer down.)
We'll get the original tteokbokki...
and the pollack roe and clam pasta.
Would the two be it? Okay.
Here.
One medium original tteokbokki and a pollack roe and clam pasta.
And a pomegranate slushy.
The previous order of medium original tteokbokki...
hasn't been served.
- It hasn't.
- It's a different order, right?
- That's right.
- Got it.
Give it a try.
(They are sharing food in the hall.)
- Don't give it to us.
- Ours is coming soon.
For goodness' sake.
(Putting out the fire for now)
Excuse me.
Do you want to keep it warm?
We have a portable burner.
- We can bring it.
- It's still hot.
- It's okay.
- Is it okay?
Okay. Let me know if you need it.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(She saw how they shared food.)
The customers at Table Two...
are having tteokbokki shared by the table next to them.
- I'll hurry. Sorry.
- Sorry.
(It doesn't go smoothly as she planned.)
Oh, dear.
(While we wait for the tteokbokki,)
(I'll make the clam pasta.)
(Orders from the village chief's and Mi Suk's tables)
(Pollack roe and clam pasta)
(A little bit of water)
(A little bit of the chicken stock)
(Add a cup of clams.)
I added the ingredients.
(She also adds a generous amount of jeolpyeon.)
(Then she stir-fries them.)
(Adding a piece of butter...)
(and two spoonfuls of pollock roe)
(After stir-frying them until her face becomes red,)
(the pollock roe covers the jeolpyeon perfectly.)
We're ready to serve it.
(Village chief's table)
(Pollack roe and clam pasta)
(Mi Suk's table)
It wasn't easy to make these.
I'm adding the roe.
It's done.
- Pastas are ready.
- Thank you.
(While the pastas are served,)
(the original tteokbokki has finally simmered down.)
(It's getting ready to be served quickly.)
It's done. The medium one is ready.
Okay.
- I'll carry it.
- Okay.
- This is the one, right?
- Yes, it is.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
(It's served right away.)
Goodness.
It's hard to run a business, isn't it?
It's okay.
(Hitting a nerve)
Here's your tteokbokki.
Okay.
Please enjoy. Sorry for keeping you waiting.
- No, it's okay.
- Sorry.
- Enjoy.
- We talked.
We talked to the village chief.
(Unlike what they said, they eat hurriedly.)
It's tasty, indeed.
(A tough critic)
(Remaining order: Original, medium)
Okay.
(In the kitchen,)
It's done.
(Mimi sets the fritters.)
Mimi, those are for the original, right?
- Yes, they are.
- Thank you.
(Young Ji checks the flavour.)
(Satisfied)
The original tastes the best.
You're so good at frying food.
- Am I?
- Yes.
Those fritters are really tasty.
(The kitchen is a bit relaxed.)
We have a moment to catch our breath now.
I'm glad to hear that.
(Space Rice Cake)
(They are the ones who said they'd be back.)
(Three people.)
(I'm a customer too.)
Please wait.
We entered this way.
I think you can go in through that door.
It's confusing.
- Hurry up.
- Go in.
Welcome.
- What? You're finally here.
- Hey.
- Welcome.
- They're here.
Right.
- We're done.
- They're good.
The tables are full now.
Have a seat. Don't stand like that.
Hello.
We'll get the original tteokbokki.
And the one with the pollack roe.
- Pollack roe...
- Just order two.
How about drinks?
What are the drinks?
(Smiling to sell some drinks)
By the way, you're pretty like those idols.
- Me? I'm an idol.
- She's an idol.
(You may have forgotten, but Yu Jin's an idol.)
You're so pretty.
- Thank you.
- A fancy coffee?
- That one.
- Coffee? Would you like a coffee?
- Their pomegranate slushy is good.
- Pomegranate slushy?
Are you having the pomegranate slushy?
A new table is here.
(Head Chef is malfunctioning again.)
- One small original tteokbokki.
- Okay.
And one pollack roe and clam pasta.
Got it.
(The kitchen team looks exhausted.)
- Everyone said it was tasty.
- I'm glad to hear that.
Are they new customers?
- Yes.
- They're new customers.
How old are they?
They are the ones who said they'd be back.
Then I'll show them what I got.
(In the meantime, Yu Jin serves the slushies.)
Here are your drinks.
Here's your coffee.
Is it possible to make it not sweet?
Yes, I can go into the container and...
Would you like to taste it and see how sweet it is?
Do you want to try it a little?
Just get me a cup.
- I'll bring it, Eun Ji.
- Okay.
(The additional order is served.)
The service team...
- is doing a great job.
- Yes.
(Eun Ji even checks the customers from time to time.)
Is it too hot for you?
Is it okay? Anybody feeling hot?
We can take off our clothes.
(Right up Eun Ji's alley)
How many clothes are you going to take off?
(Laughing)
That was very spicy.
No, it's all good.
That was great.
- Please enjoy and take your time.
- Okay.
(The customers are happy thanks to Eun Ji.)
The original tteokbokki can be served now.
(While the service team is working their magic,)
(they finished the dishes.)
Here's your pollack roe and clam pasta.
(Tasting)
The pollack roe dish is tasty.
It's tasty, isn't it?
- The rice cakes are good.
- Yes.
The rice cakes are chewy and tasty.
(Nodding)
(He is recommending the place on his phone.)
It's worth visiting once in a while, isn't it?
(Space Rice Cake is thriving.)
I'm glad we're full, Yu Jin.
I know, Eun Ji.
(Just as they breathed a sigh of relief...)
Gosh. Hello.
- Hello.
- Please come in.
- How many people?
- My gosh.
- Two?
- Hello.
(Arriving at fully booked Space Rice Cake)
If you could wait a little,
we'll contact you as soon as a table opens up.
- We have a waiting list now.
- We do?
- We have one group waiting.
- One group?
I'm not used to this kind of fame.
What? It's not at all what I expected.
(Epilogue)
- Well done.
- Well done, everyone.
Let's go home.
- Can we go back to Seoul?
- To Seoul?
- I want to go back to Seoul.
- Straighten your back.
Do you want to go back to Seoul?
- I'm scared.
- Goodness.
You wanted to make rice cakes, so we set up rice cake machines.
If you want to go back to Seoul, we'll make it happen.
- Are we going to Seoul, Young Ji?
- But our tteokbokki...
(Young Ji's joke ends up causing a huge ripple effect.)
Are we going back to Seoul?
(Coming soon)
(On next episode)
(The morning of Day 2 of business starts.)
(Let's go for it.)
(The service team's favourite part of the day)
(Grocery shopping time)
(Object 1 of desire: Headband)
(Object 2 of desire: Arm sleeves)
(Object 3 of desire: Kitchen tools)
(At that time)
(I don't know if you're aware,)
(but during the last 2 days, the service team spent 300 dollars.)
(A shocking piece of information comes in.)
(How much did you spend on groceries today?)
(The head chef begins her investigation.)
(For gimbap...)
(Did you say gimbap?)
(We need to cut down on our spending.)
(The head chef becomes sensitive about expenses tied to sales.)
(Even when deciding what to have for dinner)
(Let's check the sales first.)
(The boss's desire to make money is on another level.)
(She starts connecting everything back to sales.)
(Young Ji at Space Rice Cake)
(She's a different person.)
(A new menu to ease the boss' worries)
(A meeting of vibrant green broccoli...)
(and fresh basil)
(Broccolino Basiliano)
(A special transformation of the classic tteokbokki)
(It's also known as basil tteokbokki.)
(Tasting)
(Not only approved by the employee)
(Additional orders of Broccolino Basiliano)
(It becomes a hit with customers too.)
(Winning over everyone's taste buds, young and old)
(The ultimate new menu to escape the deficit is coming soon.)